# Bani Fahlevi

## Data Analyst

I am Bachelor's Degree from Binus University, and have professional certification in data analytics. I have 2+ years work experience as Data Analyst, and I still love to learn more about Data Analyst. I liked to analyzing data, solve the problem, and create a report with data visualization. I am really appreciate if you take the time to see my portfolio on github.

banifahlevi.github.io

✓ fahlevibani@gmail.com

**(9** 0819-1199-9991

in banifahlevi

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

PowerBI Data Report Visualization, Database Relation, Pattern & Trend Identification,

Visualization Data Insight.

**Excel** Data Analysis, PowerQuery, Pivot, Reporting Data.

**SQL** Database Design & Management, Create Data Warehouse.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **HRIS & Data Analyst**

PT. Perusahaan Perdagangan Indonesia (Persero)

Nov 2019 - Present

- Build, develop and monitor data reports required by BOD. Such as monitoring data on the movement of the number of employees.
- Processing and cleansing employee data which at first was messy and could not be processed, into appropriate data required by the system (data cleansing).
- Analyzing and processing system requirements required by the Human Capital Management department.

## **Data Analyst**

PT. Permodalan Nasional Madani (Persero)

May 2018 - Nov 2019

- Build, develop and provide weekly and daily monitoring report data for BOD needs.
- Analyzing the appropriate criteria for branch opening based on sub-district/village location points based on data on the number of KPS (pre-prosperous families).
- Build data analysis of company targets, and monitor the movement of achieving company targets.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor's Information System** 

**Binus University** 

May 2019 - Nov 2021

**Diploma Informatics Management** 

**Telkom University** 

Aug 2014 - Jan 2018